<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on jimueller</title>
    <link>http://jimueller.com/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on jimueller</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jimueller&#34;&gt;Jim Mueller&lt;/a&gt; 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:02:21 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jimueller.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ExtJS Learning Resources</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/extjs-learning-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:02:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/extjs-learning-resources/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Learning ExtJS can be a bit of a challange since, although it is well documented, there seems to be less &amp;ldquo;real world&amp;rdquo; examples available.  Since ExtJS has become more focused on the enterprise, there is less activity on typical Q&amp;amp;A platforms like Stack Overflow.  Finally, ExtJS has made major changes in its last few releases which leaves many of the examples available badly outdated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good news is that there some great resources available for learning ExtJS, in addition to Sencha&amp;rsquo;s documentation.  Some are free, but those that aren&amp;rsquo;t free are still pretty cheap for what you get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;books&#34;&gt;Books&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sencha Ext JS 6 Bootcamp in a Book: Classic Toolkit Edition&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://a.co/29HVuqp&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; by Steve Drucker of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.figleaf.com/&#34;&gt;Fig Leaf&lt;/a&gt; is in my opinion the best, most cost-effective resource available for learning ExtJS.  The book is about $60 and is basically the student guide for a weeklong course on ExtJS.  The previous version of the book, covering ExtJS 5 is &lt;a href=&#34;http://a.co/41zr5y4&#34;&gt;still available for on $25&lt;/a&gt;, and for learning ExtJS fundamentals there is no major differences.  I consider this book to be the equivelent of classes provided by Sencha, which can cost more than a $1000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book covers everything you need to build ExtJS applications if you have no ExtJS experience.  There are no gaps for a beginner and even if you have ExtJS experience it is a great way to get the complete picture of building and app and filling in any gaps you may have.  The book does have some examples of creating custom components, but it does not go in depth on more advanced ExtJS topics.  If you are strictly looking for advanced ExtJS, this is not the best book for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;extjs-documentation&#34;&gt;ExtJS Documentation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Sencha ExtJS documentation&lt;/strong&gt; is really good but in many cases you really have to know what you are looking for.  Like most SDK/API documentation, it is not going always tell you how to accomplish your goal. I&amp;rsquo;ve used the following practices to get the most out of the ExtJS docs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skim through all of the docs files to get an idea of what is available&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the search functionality and look for synonyms when trying to find specific events, methods, or properties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;View the source to view JSDuck comments that may be missing from the new docs site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn ExtJS, I spend a significant amount of time reading the docs to understand what classes were available and their purpose.  I try to take a &amp;ldquo;when in Rome&amp;rdquo; approach when using frameworks, so in an ExtJS project, I will try to find the ExtJS way of doing things.  By browsing the docs, I was able to have an idea of what framework classes could be used to accomplish a goal without resorting to using another framework like jQuery or writing my own function.  Ext has many utility classes and methods on the Ext object that can do just about anything jQuery can do, and has functions for formatting or manipulating  text.  ExtJS is a large framework and there are no shortcuts for understanding what it provides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When looking for a specific method, event, or property, it&amp;rsquo;s useful to use the search/filter tool.  Ext is pretty consistent on naming, but often it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to search for synonyms.  For example, if you are looking for the control of a component&amp;rsquo;s visibility, try searching for &amp;ldquo;visible, hidden, hide, show&amp;rdquo; so that you don&amp;rsquo;t overlook one of the class&amp;rsquo;s members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Sencha switched the docs site in late 2016, the new version has had trouble parsing out the JSDuck comments used in ExtJS source code.  This seems to be expecially true for inherited docs.  To&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>extjs utility classes</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/extjs-utility-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 11:22:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/extjs-utility-classes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>extjs currency number field</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/extjs-currency-number-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 11:21:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/extjs-currency-number-field/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switch to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/switch-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 12:52:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/switch-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Switching over the ol&amp;rsquo; blog from Jekyll to Hugo.  Hugo doesn&amp;rsquo;t suck.  Jekyll was well, a pain that always seem to break every time some gem updated.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>saving nested associated date with extjs</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/saving-nested-associated-date-with-extjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 12:56:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/saving-nested-associated-date-with-extjs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>allowing sencha cmd to serve on port 80 on linux</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/allowing-sencha-cmd-to-serve-on-port-80-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 11:20:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/allowing-sencha-cmd-to-serve-on-port-80-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve tried to serve files with Sencha Cmd on port 80, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably see an error like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;user@localhost ~/dev/extjs/extjsapp $ sencha web -p 80 start
Sencha Cmd v6.1.3.42
[INF] Starting server on port : 80
[INF] Mapping http://localhost:80/ to ....
[WRN] FAILED SelectChannelConnector@0.0.0.0:80: java.net.SocketException: Permission denied
[WRN] FAILED org.eclipse.jetty.server.Server@5d25ad3: java.net.SocketException: Permission denied
Exception in thread &amp;quot;Thread-5&amp;quot; com.sencha.exceptions.BasicException: Permission denied
	at com.sencha.exceptions.BasicException.wrap(BasicException.java:54)
	at com.sencha.exceptions.BasicException.stealthify(BasicException.java:43)
	at com.sencha.exceptions.BasicException.raise(BasicException.java:35)
	at com.sencha.util.http.Server.start(Server.java:265)
	at com.sencha.util.JettyServer.start(JettyServer.java:102)
	at com.sencha.command.filesystem.StartCommand$1.run(StartCommand.java:72)
	at com.sencha.util.ThreadUtil$1.run(ThreadUtil.java:65)
	at com.sencha.util.ThreadUtil$2.run(ThreadUtil.java:162)
	at java.lang.Thread.run(Thread.java:745)
Caused by: java.net.SocketException: Permission denied
	at sun.nio.ch.Net.bind0(Native Method)
	at sun.nio.ch.Net.bind(Net.java:433)
	at sun.nio.ch.Net.bind(Net.java:425)
	at sun.nio.ch.ServerSocketChannelImpl.bind(ServerSocketChannelImpl.java:223)
	at sun.nio.ch.ServerSocketAdaptor.bind(ServerSocketAdaptor.java:74)
	at org.eclipse.jetty.server.nio.SelectChannelConnector.open(SelectChannelConnector.java:187)
	at org.eclipse.jetty.server.AbstractConnector.doStart(AbstractConnector.java:316)
	at org.eclipse.jetty.server.nio.SelectChannelConnector.doStart(SelectChannelConnector.java:265)
	at org.eclipse.jetty.util.component.AbstractLifeCycle.start(AbstractLifeCycle.java:64)
	at org.eclipse.jetty.server.Server.doStart(Server.java:288)
	at org.eclipse.jetty.util.component.AbstractLifeCycle.start(AbstractLifeCycle.java:64)
	at com.sencha.util.http.Server.start(Server.java:263)
	... 5 more
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sencha Cmd defaults to serving files port 1841, but sometimes there is a need to serve on port 80.
One reason is if you are setting &amp;lsquo;localhost&amp;rsquo; as an allowed cross-origin domain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Linux, only root is allowed to bind processes to reserved ports - those up to 1023.  There are a few methods to get
around this, such as configuring port routing or authbind. I prefer allowing java processes to bind to port 80
by granting the &lt;code&gt;CAP_NET_BIND_SERVICE&lt;/code&gt; permission permenantly to java.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Authbind&#34;&gt;Authbind&lt;/a&gt; can be used for
one time access, and may be more appropriate if there are security concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following steps will demonstrate how to use &lt;strong&gt;setcap&lt;/strong&gt; to allow java to bind on port 80. I would prefer
to only grant Sencha Cmd with the permission, but was unable to determine how to do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, determine where java is installed, by following the symbolic links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;gt; whereis java&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The output will be similar to:
&lt;code&gt;java: /usr/bin/java /usr/share/java /usr/share/man/man1/java.1.gz&lt;/code&gt; and we see that java is in &lt;code&gt;/usr/bin/java&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at that.&lt;/p&gt;
&gt; ls -l /usr/bin/java
lrwxrwxrwx 1 root root 22 Jul 24 19:41 /usr/bin/java -&gt; /etc/alternatives/java

&lt;p&gt;We can see that &lt;code&gt;/usr/bin/java&lt;/code&gt; is a symbolic link to &lt;code&gt;/etc/alternatives/java&lt;/code&gt;, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at that.&lt;/p&gt;
&gt; ls -l /etc/alternatives/java
lrwxrwxrwx 1 root root 46 Jul 24 19:41 /etc/alternatives/java -&gt; /usr/lib/jvm/java-8-openjdk-amd64/jre/bin/java

&lt;p&gt;We can now see that the actual location of java is &lt;code&gt;/usr/lib/jvm/java-8-openjdk-amd64/jre/bin/java&lt;/code&gt;.
Now that we know where java is, we can grant permission to bind to low-numbered ports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo setcap CAP_NET_BIND_SERVICE=+eip /usr/lib/jvm/java-8-openjdk-amd64/jre/bin/java
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here we are granting with the following permissions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;e:Effictive activates the capability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;p:Permitted allows the capability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;i:Inherites the capability is inherited by child processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the &lt;code&gt;CAP_NET_BIND_SERVICE&lt;/code&gt; capability has been granted, let&amp;rsquo;s try serving on port 80.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;user@localhost ~/dev/extjs/extjsapp $ sencha web -p 80 start
Sencha Cmd v6.1.3.42
[INF] Starting server on port : 80
[INF] Mapping http://localhost:80/ to ....
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That looks much better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>easily install and update visual studio code on ubuntu</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/easily-install-and-update-visual-studio-code-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 11:22:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/easily-install-and-update-visual-studio-code-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.visualstudio.com/&#34;&gt;Visual Studio Code&lt;/a&gt;, my current go-to editor on Windows and Linux. I prefer Xubuntu for it&amp;rsquo;s combination of speed, configurability, and Git integration. It&amp;rsquo;s just a really nice editor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a relativly new product in Beta status, it&amp;rsquo;s getting fairly frequent updates. This isn&amp;rsquo;t really a problem on Windows since it has an installer to take care of updates.  This is probably true for Mac as well, but on Linux VSCode is provided as a .zip archive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The official installation instructions for Linux are to extract this .zip file to a directory and open the
&lt;strong&gt;code&lt;/strong&gt; executable.  Honestly, as a relativly novice Linux user, this method for installation isn&amp;rsquo;t very hard.  However, there is an arguably easier way, by using &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.ubuntu.com/ubuntu-make&#34;&gt;Ubuntu Make&lt;/a&gt;, which I came across on from an &lt;a href=&#34;http://askubuntu.com/a/616363&#34;&gt;answer to a question about this topic on AskUbuntu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t previously aware of Ubuntu Make, here&amp;rsquo;s the definition from the Ubuntu Wiki.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu Make is a command line tool which allows you to download the latest version of popular developer tools on your installation, installing it longside all the required dependencies (which will only ask for root access if you don&amp;rsquo;t  have all the required dependencies installed already), enable multi-arch on your system if you are on a 64 bit machine, integrate it with the Unity launcher… Basically, one command to get your system ready to develop with!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sounds great, and it is. Installing with Ubuntu Make gives the added benefits of making upgrading a one step process and making the Code icon available in menus and launchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install Ubuntu Make&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{% highlight shell %}
sudo add-apt-repository ppa:ubuntu-desktop/ubuntu-make
sudo apt-get update
sudo apt-get install ubuntu-make
{% endhighlight %}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install Visual Studio Code with Make&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;umake web visual-studio-code
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;re done, a Visual Studio Code icon will be automatically added to your launcher, and will now be available
in the Applications menu, likely under the &lt;strong&gt;Develeopment&lt;/strong&gt; folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;upgrade&#34;&gt;Upgrade&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Visual Studio Code notifies me that a newer version is available, I just run the &lt;code&gt;umake&lt;/code&gt; command again and
VS Code is updated seamlessly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;umake web visual-studio-code
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://askubuntu.com/a/616363&#34;&gt;How to install Visual Studio Code on Ubuntu?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>clean websphere portal temp directories</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/clean-websphere-portal-temp-directories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 11:21:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/clean-websphere-portal-temp-directories/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;WebSphere and WebSphere Portal create temporary directories for managing publish state, session state, and other data that can accumulate, degrading performance and causing publishing synchronization issues, especially on a development machine.  If you begin to experience slow startup times or have publishing errors from RAD, cleaning temp folders can often resolve these issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-windows-use-robocopy-to-delete-long-file-paths&#34;&gt;On Windows, use Robocopy to delete long file paths&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: On Windows, long directory paths can sometimes cause problems when trying to delete files in the WebSphere directory.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/cc733145%28WS.10%29.aspx&#34;&gt;Robocopy.exe&lt;/a&gt; is a bundled utility that has support for long file paths.  Robocopy can be used to all files in a directory by mirroring an empty directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create an empty directory.  &lt;code&gt;C:\&amp;gt;mkdir temp/empty&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using the empty directory as the &lt;strong&gt;source&lt;/strong&gt; directory, you can use Robocopy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;/MIR&lt;/code&gt; switch to mirror the empty directory, effectivly deleteing all files in the &lt;strong&gt;destination&lt;/strong&gt; directory.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;gt;robocopy.exe C:\temp\empty C:\folder\to\delete\ /MIR&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop the server.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;profile_root/wstemp
profile_root/temp
profile_root/logs
profile_root/tranlog&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>howto install fme dqman without documentum client</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/howto-install-fme-dqman-without-documentum-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 11:22:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/howto-install-fme-dqman-without-documentum-client/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During a development project, I needed to run fme&amp;rsquo;s dqMan to query Documentum, but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to install the Documentum client as well.  The following procedure shows how to get the required Documentum files off of an existing install so dqMan can run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The following procedure is for Documentum 6.5, it may be applicable for other versions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fme-us.com/technologies/ecm/emc-documentum/dqman/&#34;&gt;dqMan&lt;/a&gt; from the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fme-us.com/&#34;&gt;fme&lt;/a&gt; website.  You will receive the license file in an email.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extract and install dqMan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From the content server, copy the &lt;code&gt;dmcl.dll&lt;/code&gt; file from the &lt;code&gt;Documentum\product\6.5\bin&lt;/code&gt; directory to a location on your system Path.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create a dmcl.ini file and place the following section.&lt;/p&gt;
[DOCBROKER_PRIMARY]
host=yourContentServer #IP or Hostname&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create and Environmental Variable named &lt;code&gt;DCML_CONFIG&lt;/code&gt; that points to the &lt;code&gt;dmcl.ini&lt;/code&gt; file.  E.g. &lt;code&gt;C:\dmcl.ini&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>use putty with console2</title>
      <link>http://jimueller.com/post/use-putty-with-console2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 20:49:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimueller.com/post/use-putty-with-console2/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sourceforge.net/projects/console/files/&#34;&gt;Console2&lt;/a&gt; is a great
frontend on Windows for cmd.exe and PowerShell.  It
provides re-sizable windows, a tabbed interface, and transparent
windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can also be used with
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/putty/&#34;&gt;PuTTY&lt;/a&gt;, but it
takes a little bit of work.  The issue is apparently with ANSI escape
codes. Thankfully David A. Sjøen
(&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/dasjoen/&#34;&gt;@dasjoen&lt;/a&gt;) commented on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hanselman.com/blog/Console2ABetterWindowsCommandPrompt.aspx&#34;&gt;Scott
Hanselman’s Console2
article&lt;/a&gt;
with the solution using ANSICON.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/adoxa/ansicon#readme&#34;&gt;ANSICON ReadMe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ANSICON provides ANSI escape sequences for Windows console programs.
It provides much the same functionality as `ANSI.SYS’ does for
MS-DOS. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Download ANSICON (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/adoxa/ansicon/downloads&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;) and extract the
contents from the &lt;code&gt;x86&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;x64&lt;/code&gt; folders to your Console2 installation
folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I now have the following files in my &lt;code&gt;C:\Program Files\Console2\&lt;/code&gt;
directory:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ANSI32.dll&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ANSI64.dll&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ansicon.exe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ANSI-LLW.exe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open Console2 and create a new tab with the command line, replacing &lt;code&gt;aPuttyProfileName&lt;/code&gt; with the &lt;a href=&#34;http://the.earth.li/~sgtatham/putty/0.63/htmldoc/Chapter7.html#plink&#34;&gt;name of a saved PuTTY profile&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
C:\Program Files\Console2\ansicon.exe &#34;C:\Program Files (x86)\PuTTY\plink.exe&#34;
-load aPuttyProfileName&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>